[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 58, "question": "Why when Americans are about to vote now is he the guy to do the most important thing, turn round America's economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "WRB", "NNPS", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 59, "answer": "He knows how to fix things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 67, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "I'm not sure where you got your facts but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Why not say, my dad is going to crush him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Pull off a Chris Christie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1 trillion"]}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 142, "question": "What comfort can you give young women that think that your father is going to come after them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 143, "answer": "If we keep spending $1 trillion a year more than we take in, and we keep saddling this country and the future generations with debt, none of those things matter.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":"], "qSentId": 207, "question": "How do you feel about this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "This is --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": ".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 224, "question": "Who's One Direction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 225, "answer": "Not good at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Have you begun to think about what that could be like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "We really don't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Do you feel, though, that there's been a real change since that last debate, that there's been an irrational reaction in your father's favor because of the way he performed and indeed, the poor way that the president performed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "So much enthusiasm.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "And what happens?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Very aggressive as teenagers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "And by the way, where is Ben?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "He's busy being a doctor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 293, "question": "A bunch of malarkey?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 294, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "It's Irish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "(INAUDIBLE) Mitt Romney across the stage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "No, not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "You would have been equally unimpressed, wouldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Well -- well, I would push back on that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ":", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Why is this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "Well, let me say -- let me say this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 393, "question": "What on earth makes you think I fantasize about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 394, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "How did it go, the meeting with Mitt Romney?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "It was a nice meeting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "I think you were raised Roman Catholic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I was, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Do you think he is a Christian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Well, first of all, I'm not going to get into what each candidate believes or they don't believe.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "All wondering -- but they're all wondering if we vote for this guy, are we voting for somebody who essentially is a Christian?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBG", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 484, "question": "Don't you think it's a quite interesting debate, though?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 485, "answer": "You ask him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 498, "question": "Do you have any problem with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 499, "answer": "No, because I think as we get older, Piers, we do change our views.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Gay marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "The definition of marriage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Why shouldn't gay people get married?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Listen, they can do whatever they want.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Can they get married or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "Do you think it's a sin, homosexuality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "Yes, sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "Anything you want to share with me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "I'm glad my mother's not here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "How's your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "He's doing well, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Have your worst fears been realized?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Even beyond my worst fears.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "I do agree with that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Do you see that in him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "I doubt seriously whether that's, in fact, what has happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "Not at this late stage.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "What did you make of that, in particular the way the White House behaved in the aftermath?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Well, I think we have to allow for some light and shade and some perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Is she just taking the heat away from Obama tomorrow night, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Exactly.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Obama"], "TIME": ["tomorrow night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 642, "question": "In all your experience, is it credible that the White House, the president, the vice president, would have no knowledge of any requests from an embassy for extra security, particularly in a hot spot like Libya, where there's been so much attention from the White House in the last year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 643, "answer": "I can certainly see where someone else would have a different view, but I think it is credible, particularly in the heat of an election campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House", "White House"], "LOCATION": ["Libya"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 654, "question": "Or do you think it suited the agenda of the administration to not have this as a reminder that al Qaeda's alive and well and killing Americans?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "JJ", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 655, "answer": "Two points.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "Quick reaction to that, Dan?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "TO", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "ATHER: Playing defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "Skillfully, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "As skillfully as possible under the circumstances.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 711, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 712, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "WP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "WRB", "NN", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 717, "question": "And how does the president that wins in three weeks time put it right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 718, "answer": "TEWART: What happened really, I think, was that manufacturing went where labor was cheap and more plentiful, and more amenable to hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 735, "question": "Is the genie out of the bottle, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 736, "answer": "Well, I think it can come back.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Do you that think he's in that big a hole?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "I think it's a big debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121015pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 763, "question": "What's the website?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 764, "answer": "MarthaStewart.com.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]